Pathi Saritha

"Supply Chain Data Analyst"

Singapore

- Email me on Indeed: http://www.indeed.com/r/Pathi-Saritha/aa0ff971069dc61d
- · Singaporean, .
- Bachelor of Science in Mathematics, Statistics & Computer Applications.

Graduate Diploma in Business & Finance.

• Currently working as "Supply Chain Data Analyst" for Cummins Asia Pte Ltd.

Total 6 years of working experience in Operations Support which includes Data crunching and Analysis, Regular & ad hoc reports generation and Database Management. Liaise between Vendors and Operations department to resolve complex customers issues related to internal operations such as data inconsistency, new report's needs, spot analysis.

- Meticulous, figure sensitive and good in problem solving.
- Proficient in Microsoft Access & Excel (Pivot Table, VLOOKUP, Marcos, VBA) and SQL programming.

•

Notice Period: Immediately

Resume of SARITHA

Mail: psarithareddy@yahoo.com

Mobile No: 81136405

Am having over 6 years of working experience in Operations Support which includes Data crunching and Analysis, Regular & ad hoc reports generation and Database Management. Liaise between Vendors and Operations department to resolve complex customers issues related to internal operations such as data inconsistency, new report's needs, spot analysis.

Work Experience

"Supply Chain Data Analyst"

Cummins Asia Pte Ltd October 2018 to March 2019

6 Months Contract)

Responsibilities:

- Set up efficient process for Data crunching to manage large chunks of data.
- Perform data Analysis & present data in multiple formats and generate Reports for Operations Management.
- Deep dive to resolve the data mismatch issues and validate against propriety Order Management System.

IT Executive

Integrated Health Plans Pte Ltd September 2007 to April 2013

IHP)', a division of 'Ezyhealth Holdings Pte Ltd'.

Reason for Leaving: To prepare for the exams for "Graduate Diploma In Business And Finance"

Responsibilities:

- Generate Payment consolidation Reports by reconciling the records of billed claims & the payments made.
- Generate Monthly Revenue Reports to realize the earnings from potential customers.
- Perform Trend Analysis to determine the pattern of clinical claims & Leaves used by Employees
- Liaise with internal departments (Operations, Finance) and Clients for Reporting requirements.
- Perform data integrity verification checks using SQL Queries.
- Generate Custom Reports using Crystal Reports, MS Access & Excel.
- Daily support & maintenance of in-house Applications.

Recognitions:

- Identified the lapse in internal workflow of invoice processing. Proposed the revised workflow to management, which saved S\$ 15K pa.
- Studied internal work processes & simplified the day to day task execution using basic IT Tools, which helped Operations Executives to perform the transactions faster & in a more accurate manner.
- > Worked as an IT Operations Specialist from Aug 2014 to March 2015 for 'ST Electronics (Info-Software Systems) Pte Ltd'

Reason for Leaving: To take care of the kids.

Responsibilities:

- Monitor, manage and maintain the DC operation and facilities.
- Plan and manage equipment movement and hosting.
- Liaise with the vendors on maintenance and enhancement issues.
- Plan and perform System Maintenance and OS/Application Software Patches.
- Troubleshoot and report system incidents and abnormalities.
- Documentation and Reporting.

Education

Bachelor of Science in Mathematics

Kakatiya University

Skills

ACCESS (5 years), EXCEL (5 years), MS ACCESS (5 years), SQL (5 years), DATABASE (Less than 1 year)

Additional Information

Technical Skills:

- Proficient in Microsoft Access & Excel
- Programming Skills: Visual Basic & SQL
- Database: Microsoft Access & SQL Server 2012

Strengths

- Having ability to work under pressure to meet the deadlines, while maintaining the quality of deliverables.
- Enhance internal workflow by automating the repeated tasks for effective utilization of resources.

Other Details: